Guide to the Larry John Meyers Papers, 1980-2015 CTC.2012.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pittsburgh Productions, 1980-2015; III.
  - Pittsburgh Irish & Classical Theatre, 2002-2014
    - The Gigli Concert, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Author: Tom Murphy Director: Andrew S. Paul Performance Dates: May 30 - June 15, 2002
    - Great Expectations, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Heartbreak House, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
      Author: George Bernard Shaw Director: George Lehane Performance Dates: June 2 - 25, 2005
    - Henry, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Author: Thomas Kilroy Performance Dates: Stage Reading October 11 - 12, 2004
    - Henry, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Author: Thomas Kilroy Director: Andrew S. Paul Performance Dates: August 31 - September 24, 2005
    - The Hot House, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
      Author: Harold Pinter Director: Matthew Gray Performance Dates: July 22 - August 22, 2021
    - Jane Eyre, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Author: Charlotte Bronte Adapted by: Alan Stanford Director: Scott Wise Performance Dates: December 3 - 20, 2009
    - Julius Caesar, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Author: Shakespeare Director: Andrew S. Paul Performance Dates: April 11 - 28, 2007
    - King Lear, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
      Author: William Shakespeare Director: James Christy Performance Dates: April 12 - 26, 2008
    - Othello, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Author: William Shakespeare Director: Andrew S. Paul Performance Dates: May 22 - June 12, 2010
    - Pitmen Painters, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
      Author: Lee Hall Director: Andrew S. Paul Performance Dates: May 31 - June 23, 2012
    - Stuff Happens, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Author: David Hare Director: Andrew S. Paul Performance Dates: May 12 - June 2, 2007
    - That Time, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Author: Samuel Beckett Director: Andrew S. Paul Performance Dates: September 10, 2006
    - Three Sisters, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
      Author: Anton Chekhov Director: Harriet Power Performance Dates: July 19 - August 26, 2012
      This folder includes promotional materials and reviews from Funny Chekhov and Ivanov.
    - Travesties, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
      Author: Tom Stoppard Director: Gregory Lehane Performance Dates: June 3 - 19, 2004
    - Uncle Vanya, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Author: Anton Chekhov Director: Andrew S. Paul Performance Dates: August 12 - September 4, 2004
  - Pittsburgh Playhouse, 1999-2012
    - Ah, Wilderness, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Author: Eugene O'Neill Director: Robert A. Miller Performance Dates: September 6 - 23, 2007
    - Halcyon Days, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      Author: Steven Dietz Director: David Wheeler Performance Dates: September 2 - 21, 2003
    - Hamlet, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Author: Shakespeare Director: Rick Kemp Performance Dates: May 9 - June 1, 2003
    - The Heiress, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
      Authors: Ruth Goetz and Augustus Goetz Director: Larry John Meyers Performance Dates: January 22 - February 9, 1997
    - Ithaka, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Author: Botho Straus Translated by: Howard Burman Director: Ronald Allan-Lindblom Performance Dates: January 16 - February 13, 2000
    - MIA: Missing in Action, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
      Author: Bruce J. Robinson Director: John Amplas Performance Dates: March 23 - April 7, 2012
    - On the Beach, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Author: Howard Burman Director: Ronald Allan-Lindblom Performance Dates: September 15 - October 3, 1999
    - Undoing Salk, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Author: Robert Benedetti Director: Robert Benedetti Performance Dates: February 3 - 22, 2004
  - Pittsburgh Public Theater, 1983-2015
    - 1776, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
      Author: Peter Stone Music and Lyrics: Sherman Edwards Director: Ted Pappas Performance Dates: January 24 - February 24, 2013
    - Amadeus, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
      Author: Peter Shaffer Director: Ted Pappas Performance Dates: January 24 - February 24, 2008
    - Amazing Grace, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Author: Michael Cristofer Director: Edward Gilbert Performance Dates: October 12 - November 19, 1995
    - Awake and Sing!, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Author: Clifford Odets Director: Elina de Santos Performance Dates: April 25 - May 26, 2002
    - Born Yesterday, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Author: Garson Kanin Director: Ted Pappas Performance Dates: September 27 - October 28, 2012
    - Broadway: The Play, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
      Authors: George Abbott and Philip Dunning Director: Ted Pappas Performance Dates: September 23 - October 24, 2004
    - Gem of the Ocean, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
      Author: August Wilson Director: Reggie Life Performance Dates: May 25 - June 25, 2006
    - Harry's Friendly Service, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
      Author: Rob Zellars Director: Ted Pappas Performance Dates: May 28 - June 28, 2009
      This folder also contains CDs and photographs from the production.
    - A History of the American Film, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Author: Christopher Durang Director: Larry Arrick Performance Dates: October 28 - December 11, 1983
    - Joe Turner's Come and Gone, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      Author: August Wilson Director: Claude Purdy Performance Dates: September 7 - October 22, 1989
    - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
      Author: August Wilson Director: Claude Purdy Performance Dates: September 17 - November 1, 1992
      This production also contains photographs from the production.
    - Mad Forest: A Play from Romania, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
      Author: Caryl Churchill Director: Mark Wing-Davey Performance Dates: December 30, 1992 - February 7, 1993
    - A Moon for the Misbegotten, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
      Author: Eugene O'Neill Director: Lee Sankowich Performance Dates: April 23 - May 31, 1992
      This folder contains photographs from the production.
    - The Night of the Iguana, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      Author: Tennessee Williams Director: Claude Purdy Performance Dates: September 27 - November 4, 1990
    - Nora-Julie, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Author: Ingmar Bergman Director: Larry Arrick Performance Dates: February 17 - April 1, 1984
    - Othello, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
      Author: William Shakespeare Director: Ted Pappas Performance Dates: April 16 - May 17, 2015
    - Our Town, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
      Author: Thornton Wilder Director: Robert Allan Ackerman Performance Dates: November 12 - December 23, 1990
    - Our Town, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      Author: Thronton Wilder Director: Ted Pappas Performance Dates: September 26 - October 27, 2013
    - The Royal Family, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      Author: George S. Kaufman Director: Ted Pappas Performance Dates: September 30 - October 31, 2010
    - Stayers and Goers (Box 20, Folder 5)
      Author: Todd Kreidler Director: Larry John Meyers Performance Dates: November 17, 2008
    - Three Sisters, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      Author: Anton Chekhov Adapted by: Corinne Jacker Director: Bill Gardner Performance Dates: January 23 - March 1, 1992
    - Waiting for Godot, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Author: Samuel Beckett Director: Larry Arrick Performance Dates: April 6 - May 20, 1984
  - Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, 1998
    - Gershwin!, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      Text by: Jonathan Bolt Conductor: Marvin Hamlisch Performance Dates: June 11 - 14, 1998
  - Quantum Theatre, 2010-2014
    - Madagascar, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Author: J.T. Rogers Director: Sheila McKenna Performance Dates: January 31 - February 16, 2014
    - The Task, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      Author: Heiner Müller Translated by: Carl Weber Director: Jed Allen Harris Performance Dates: April 22 - May 9, 2010
  - Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival, 1981-1990
    - 1981 TRSF (Box 21, Folder 3)
      Productions: The Comedy of Errors, The Winters Tale, As You Like It Author: Shakespeare Directors: Gillette A. Elvgren, Jr., Kathleen E. George, Kathleen Conlin Performance Dates: June 18 - August 16, 1981
    - 1982 TRSF (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Productions: The Tragedy of Hamlet: Prince of Denmark, The Merry Wives of Windsor, The Tempest Author: Shakespeare Directors: Kathleen E. George, Marc Masterson, Jed Allen Harris Performance Dates: June 17 - August 15, 1982
    - 1983 TRSF (Box 21, Folder 5)
      Productions: Henry the Fourth, Much Ado About Nothing, Othello Author: Shakespeare Directors: W. Stephen Coleman, Gillette A. Elvgren, Jr., Marc Masterson Performance Dates: June 16 - August 14, 1983
    - 1990 TRSF (Box 21, Folder 6)
      Production: Richard II Author: Shakespeare Director: Stephen Coleman Performance Dates: June 22 - July 14, 1990
  - University of Pittsburgh Repertory Theatre, 1998-2012
    - The Gammage Project, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
      Author: Attilio Favorini Director: Mark Clayton Southers Performance Dates: February 9 - 19, 2012
    - The Hudsucker Proxy, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Authors: Joel Coen, Ethan Coen, and Sam Raimi Director: Robert C.T. Steele Performance Dates: November 3 - 21, 1999
    - Moby Dick, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Author: Orson Welles Director: Robert C.T. Steele Performance Dates: March 28 - April 15, 2001
    - Our Town, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Author: Thornton Wilder Director: Kathleen E. George Performance Dates: March 31 - April 18, 1999
    - Pericles, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Author: William Shakespeare Director: Larry John Meyers Performance Dates: February 11 - 22, 1998
    - Waiting for Godot, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Author: Samuel Beckett Director: W. Stephen Coleman Performance Dates: September 19 - October 7, 2001